gdev.com 2012-06-10

# Privacy Policy | Devfactory

## Your Privacy Rights

DevFactory FZ-LLC ("DevFactory FZ") is pleased to provide this disclosure regarding its limited use of information generated from this website. 

## What this Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how DevFactory FZ treats personal information, if any, collected and received through DevFactory FZ's website. Personal information is information that can be used to identify a person that is not in the public domain. Examples include your name, address, e-mail address, and other information not publicly available. 

This policy does not govern the practices of entities that DevFactory FZ does not own or control, or entities that do not own or control DevFactory FZ or people that DevFactory FZ does not employ or manage. 

## Information Collection and Use

DevFactory FZ may automatically receive and record information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address and cookies. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information. DevFactory FZ may use information that we collect about you to: (i) deliver the products and services that you have requested; (ii) manage your customer relationship and provide you with customer support; (iii) perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others; (iv) communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, or other third parties; (v) develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other websites; (vi) verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions, contests and sweepstakes; (vii) enforce our terms and conditions; (viii) manage our business; (ix) perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and (x) sell or transfer individual information to third parties for any legally permissible purpose in DevFactory FZ’s sole discretion. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

DevFactory FZ uses industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged between DevFactory FZ and other companies to help ensure its security. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under DevFactory FZ's control. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

If this site contains links to other sites, DevFactory FZ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

## Third Parties and Cookies

DevFactory FZ sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements and web usage. DevFactory FZ's privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). 

Many of DevFactory FZ's web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell DevFactory FZ your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to DevFactory FZ by, for example, registering at one of DevFactory FZ's sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on DevFactory FZ's sites. DevFactory FZ also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. 

DevFactory FZ and third parties may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to DevFactory FZ's cookie policy. 

## Links

DevFactory FZ may create links to other web sites. DevFactory FZ will make a reasonable effort to link only to sites that meet similar standards for maintaining each individual's right to privacy. However, many other sites that are not associated with or authorized by DevFactory FZ may have links leading to DevFactory FZ's site. DevFactory FZ cannot control these links and DevFactory FZ is not responsible for any content appearing on these sites. Since this website does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. DevFactory FZ encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

## Amendments

DevFactory FZ may amend this policy at any time. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact DevFactory FZ at: [webmaster@DevFactoryFZ.com](mailto:webmaster@DevFactoryFZ.com)
